[{"answer": "We are reassessing and re-evaluating.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "Is that your message?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "We are re-evaluating and reassessing.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "But are you staying in the race?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "We'll be making a decision in the next several days.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "How soon until we have a final answer on your future plans?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "Well, it's hard for me to know.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Is he toast?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know about sympathy at all.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Do you feel sympathy for him?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Well, probably not.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "Never mind Washington but to the electorate as they used to be?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Well, I guess you could compare it to many others that have done this.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "What do you make of this?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Well, time will tell.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "I mean if this has the desired effect on the global economy and impacts favorably on jobs, is Barack Obama sitting pretty?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "I'm doing great, Piers.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "Senator, how are you?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "I love this preoccupation with national polls.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "What are you going to do to save the day for your campaign?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "ANTORUM: Well, what Karen and I do in all of these races is we pray for all of the folks who have to go through this very difficult process.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "What do you think of Herman Cain's crisis that he's in, where he's being hit with this slew of sexual allegations?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "It's very difficult.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "How's it been for you in particular living with this and having to run for president?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Well, I think that a fair question and I think it really requires us to really understand how sexual abuse by authority figures like Sandusky coerced silence and secrecy and shame, and cause this survivor and other victims like him to really believe that they're being cared for and to believe that it's their fault.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "I suppose the obvious question, why did your client keep his silence all these years?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Well, what he feels and what every survivor feels when they hear that kind of denial and minimization is fury, because there is a tendency of people like we just heard to want to believe the most powerful and effective among us like Jerry Sandusky wouldn't do something like this.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "I mean what does your client feel when he hears that Jerry is just a big old kid?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "Well, what I feel is important as what we need to really do and the question we need to ask first is why did Jerry Sandusky for as long as he did be allowed to do what he did for decades to so many kids while so many people around him saw the signs or got the reports and did nothing, and chose instead to protect him and the institution.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "And what should happen to it now?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Well, I think a lot of mistruths have been written about Phoebe and I think that it was time to take her back to reclaim her as ours and to put an end to some of the stories that have been going around.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Why are you doing it?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "Very much so.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Were you taken back by the kind of worldwide attention?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "'BRIEN: I was taking a career break.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "What was -- what was the motivation?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "No, not really.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "How they would adapt?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Extraordinarily intelligent and vivacious and great sense of humor.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "What kind of girl was she, Phoebe?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "In ways, she was.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "Was she a confident girl?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "The reason I ask is I think crucially to how this all play out, when you enrolled Phoebe at the school, you did tell the officials that she was susceptible to bullying?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "Phoebe, she had -- she had a run in with some girls before.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "What had happened before that made you feel that?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "In Ireland?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Oh, that will be no problem.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "What did they say to you?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "So they knew.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "And one of the vice principals was called on a personal call and asked to keep an eye out for Phoebe?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "November.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "When did you discover for the first time that Phoebe was being bullied?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "Well, once, in December, she told me that one of the girls involved in a new incident of bullying kept coming up to her in the hallways and screaming at her.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "What could you deduce?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "But she wasn't -- the bullying on Facebook, the cyber bullying that has been put out by people, was just a small component of the bullying of Phoebe.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Did you know that these girls were using social media like Facebook and so on to bully her as well?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, it is.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "This is a systematic abuse of somebody, isn't it?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "Or \"she got what she deserved,\" that was another one.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "To drive somebody to suicide and they just but \"done\" on Facebook?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "I -- I honestly don't know.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Why were they so determined to force Phoebe into what eventually happened?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "It's -- it's astounding that there was never a stop mechanism, you know, internal stop mechanism for some of these kids, to say this is going too far.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "It's wicked, isn't it?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "It was -- it was very painful because, you know, you realize as a parent that no matter what I did, no matter how many times I called the school, no matter how many people I might have spoken to there, that she didn't stand a chance there.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "What is your reaction when you see again Guy Sayer saying that so soon after Phoebe died?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "As a mother, I think that had the school intervened the way they should have intervened, if they had followed up the way they should have followed up, that Phoebe would still be here.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "And as a mother?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "I'd like to actually clarify, because I know that there are some journalist that think that prison terms were on the cards.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "Do you feel that justice was done?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Has she ever said anything to you, Sharon Velazquez?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Nothing?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Never wrote to you?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Did any of them write to you?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Did you feel that remorse was sincere?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Did you pick up on that?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Well, they were tried as youthful offenders, those that fit our -- that were under the age of 17.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "What have been the implications of that for future cases now involving bullying?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "Essentially what it does is mandate the schools to report incidences of bullying, should they believe that that -- an act is one of bullying.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "In simple terms, what that is law?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Well, ideally, I would like it to be that humans just treat each other in a civilized manner and no boundaries.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "What would you like the legacy to be?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "No I -- no, I'm not.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "You're not?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "111130pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "And actually if the legacy is that, in future, schools are just more aware, they take more action earlier, and some lives can be saved rather than lost, because of what's happened, that is at least a positive that comes out of this hell for you, isn't it?", "qSentId": 549}]